

+57 302 515 3000

angellylopezz@gmail.com

EDUCATION

Digital marketing Domestika 2024

Community manager Politecnico superior 2024

Foreign Language (B2 English)
Colombo Americano Institute
2023

Barchelor's Degree in Nursing

2003-2005

SKILLS

Branding

Graphic Design

Writing

Communication & teamwork

Social media management

LANGUAGE

Spanish (Native)

English (B2)

ANGELLY LÓPEZ

Community Manager

ABOUT ME

I am a highly skilled communicator with a background in the medical field. After retiring from my previous role for personal reasons, I have harnessed my communication and writing skills to embark on a new carrer as a Digital Marketing Manager, and an Advertising Editor. My journey began as a freelancer, designing and writing advertising campaigns for friends and acquaintances who recommended my work. Currently, I am pursuing a postgraduate degree in Community Management to further enhance my expertise.

WORK EXPERIENCE

O^{2023 - Currently} Freelance l

Social Media Manager

- Directed all operations to ensure the success and profitability of companies and brands
- Designed advertising materials and created promotional strategies for clients.
- Translated texts form English to Spanish.
- This role required excellent communication and writing skills to achieve succesful outcomes.

2022- 2023 QuickMedia | Cali, Colombia.

ODigital Marketing Assistant

- Developed advertising campaigns from scratch for gyms.
- Communicated effectively with clients to reach successful agreements.

2012-2013

Valle del Lili Fundation Hospital | Cali,

Colombia.

Registered Nurse

- Provided comprehensive medical and nursing care to patients.
- Administered medications and treatments as prescribed.
- Conducted health assessments and documented patient histories.
- Worked under pressure in a fast-paced environment.
- Collaborated effectively with healthcare teams to ensure optimal patient care.
- Developed strong interpersonal skills and a deep understanding of patient needs.
- Gained extensive knowledge in medicine and healthcare.

2014 - 2015

Baxter Labs

Occupational Health Assistant

- Attention to employees in the medical assistance area.
- Scheduling of medical consultations.